Hi, I'm Honchu Akimoto, the Ice Cream Man!
I'm sure you're all wondering what's going on, right?
It's downstairs.
And, and, and, and...
Bubba bubba bubba bubba!
Kachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachacha!
Today's the day.
I'd like to do something exciting and thrilling
I'm going to do something exciting!
Let's call it
Which is left or right?
I wonder what it will taste like!
It's all right!
What do you mean by "left or right"?
First of all, take this ice cream.
and add various toppings to it.
toppings to make a delicious ice cream.
Speaking of which...
I didn't see it.
I was asked, "Which one do you want, the left or the right? He asked me if I wanted the left or the right.
I said right.
I'd say right, and then I'd put this on the right, and then I'd put this on the left.
And then I'll put it on the right side and put it on the left side.
What kind of flavor of ice cream will I get?
That's what you do, right?
That's right.
Eeeeee!
So I don't know how it will turn out.
But from what I've seen...
It's all really good food.
Spoon.
Melted
Cashew almond
chocolate chip
coconut
Cocoa powder
Almond slices
Muciamagri
sweet potato
Apple jam
Nutella
I have this chocolate sauce and honey.
and honey!
I thought it was all pretty good...
But there's a problem.
This?
It's just apples.
It depends on the combination.
What? What flavor? I don't know.
Chocolate, maybe.
It's all good, right?
The other day...
I had an ice cream called Azuki Chocolate.
It was really good.
So I think I can handle it.
I think I can tolerate honey.
Honey apple might be really good.
That's the only thing.
I'm not sure how it'll turn out with cocoa powder.
It's what happens.
It's what happens when you choose this one.
Nutella.
I've never heard the word "Nutella" before. It sounds like a Pokemon name. Nutella.
It's a hazelnut spread with cocoa.
It's a famous series. Everyone on the staff knew about it, but I didn't.
I'm a little curious.
I'm supposed to close my eyes, right?
Yes, that's right.
Okay, let's see how it's going to be.
Well, close your eyes.
Let's have fun.
Right or left?
I really don't know.
Uh, left!
This way?
First one.
Oh!
This one?
Yes, sir.
Two more?
Two more.
What?
Yes, right or left?
Huh?
Right!
This way, right?
Yes, sir.
Oh, wow! Isn't it good?
Coconut and almonds are absolutely delicious!
Then maybe we'll do it for the last item?
Yes, please.
Okay, last item, right or left?
Oh, I don't know what to do.
Right!
Yes...
Oh!
But I think it'll work.
Oh, let's make it then!
By the way...
It's this way!
It's definitely this way!
Yes, it is.
You might discover something new.
There might be.
Then I'm excited about the Gummie pack!
I've never bought one of these.
Oh!
Four of a kind.
Interesting.
I'll put these in.
Please open this one.
Ah! Ah!
It looks good.
Now, the jam...
Ah!
Oh, nice sound!
apple
Jaaam.
No, thank you.
Whoa!
It's good, right?
It's got a lot of pulp in it. Jam.
Yes, and almond slices.
Oh, that looks good.
Looks delicious.
And here we go.
Exhibit name, vanilla apple jam with almond coconut.
Doesn't it look like a very high quality ice cream?
It looks so good!
Let's try some!
Taste it!
Bon appétit!
Mmm!
Mmm?
Mmm! Delicious!
This could be the best combination ever.
What? We have a menu!
Vanilla and apple jam would definitely go well together.
The pulp is so nice.
It's got a nice crunch to it.
With this thin drink.
It's hard.
It's hard, and it tastes like coconut.
Two different kinds of crunchiness and
flavors come together.
I'm in. I'm in.
If there's anybody out there that's an ice cream man, I'd love to hear from you.Anyone, okay, if you are an ice cream maker.
Please use this!
Great success!
You may never go over this again.
Remember the last time you tasted it.
Mmm! Mmm! It's delicious!
Oh, I'm so excited! Next!
Let's go for the second round!
Please!
Okay, first round.
Okay, which way, right or left?
Left!
This way, right?
Yes!
I wanted chocolate! I've been there before! The last time was nice, gentle.
What shall we do next time? Aah!
That's too much!
Yes, right? Left? Which way? Right!
Oh! Congratulations!
Uh, yeah, I think that's good! What did I do?
A tweet! Aah! Well, I guess you're both right!
And the future is still bright!
Yes, right, which way?
Heh heh heh heh.
Ta-da!
Right!
Ooh!
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Mmm.
Wow, wow, yo, let's go!
Let's go!
But there's a can of krion.
Oh, I see.
I wonder how to put krion cans in the right way.
Ice cream.
I'm looking forward to it!
Next...
What is it? This is it, isn't it?
I've never done this before.
Cutting yoga with a spoon.
Yes, sir.
I'm not very good at toppings.
And canned chestnuts
I love chestnuts!
What the hell is this?
Everything is black this time.
Because you had so many white ones.
And chocolate chip.
It looks good.
Here it is!
Vanilla chestnut chip.
Yes!
I'd like to hear this all in one bite.
Bon appétit!
Mmmmmmmmmmmm!
Yokan goes away first.
Chestnut remains.
Chestnut is so strong!
The chocolate chip tastes like chestnut.
You can't taste the chocolate.
It's just crunchiness and texture.
It's delicious.
It's all good stuff, so it's delicious.
Maybe it's good in its own way.
Mm-hmm. Delicious.
But you know, I didn't think the chestnuts would be so strong
I feel like yokan is stronger than yokan, right?
There's something gone
the taste of the yokan.
It's not so much the taste as the texture.
If I compare it to these two...
I'd rather eat yokan.
I like yokan too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I just felt it for the first time.
Oh, it's delicious!
Let's eat Ryokan as it is
I've come to a conclusion
And the cucumber is delicious!
Well, it might have tasted better earlier
And it was delicious because it was a flavor I've never had before in that combination.
It was a good feeling.
There are a lot of things to discover.
I'll go to the last one.
I'll take the last one.
This is fun.
I wonder...
I wonder.
Left or right? Left! This way, this way.
Oh! I wanted to try it! I especially like the smell of this one.
Next!
Okay, left or right? Left!
Ooh! Oh, wait! Wait, I don't know!
Yes! Okay, last one!
Okay, left or right? Right!
Oh! There it is!
Oh!
One of the options was this way.
Nutella.
I'll make it!
If this one really goes well with it...
Found it!
Baked sweet potatoes and honey go well together.
What about baked sweet potatoes and chocolate?
But, well...
Maybe not chocolate.
Maybe we're getting off on the wrong foot here.
It's a chunky ice cream.
The ice cream itself is delicious.
All right!
Here you go.
Okay, then.
Let's start with the sweet potatoes.
Ha!
They're so cute.
Not like a candy sweet potato, more like a sun-dried sweet potato.
This is definitely okay so far.
Oh! Beautiful!
And here's some cocoa powder.
How fancy! This could be good!
Well, yes! It's done!
Vanilla Imomitsu Cocoa!
Now, I'd like to go to the place where you can taste all the sweet potato honey cocoa!
Oh!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's so good!
The honey brings out the sweetness of the sweet potato even more, doesn't it?
If it's just the sweetness of the sweet potato, the sweetness of the ice cream and the sweetness of the sweet potato will disappear.
It makes it so much sweeter.
And the cocoa powder gives it a bit of bitterness. And the cocoa powder gives it a bit of bitterness.
What?
I think this is the best. This is the best! Yay! Yeah! I found it! That's good. That's a great find.
Yeah, it's delicious! But with the sweet potato in there, it's like you're eating something that's sweet potato, solid, right?
It's like eating a hokey thing, it's delicious!
Because of the ice cream, it tastes Western, all the way Western.
I don't feel any harmony.
Delicious!
If there was a crepe with this flavor, I might eat it!
I love it. This is it.
Do you remember the first one?
At first it was apple, coconut, almond...
It was good, but now I think it's a little bland.
I mean, I've never had anything like it before.
It's gone over the top.
But then there was this delicious new cocoa.
Oh, this is fun.
Oh, good, give it a try.
Maybe even add some chocolate chips.
Adds texture.Texture Plus
and apple tart
Bon appétit!
Yum! Yummmmmmmm!
Delicious!
It's just the texture, but the taste, not the flavor...
Then I guess the three kinds we have now are enough.
Yay! So much fun!
I've made some good discoveries!
This time, though, I think I was relatively gentle.
Everything tasted good and went well together.
I wonder what would be a little bit like that... like soy sauce or vanilla with soy sauce...
If it all came together in a nice way, we might soon have an invention.
I'd love to do it again sometime. Lovely project.
Good, I could do it.
And we had some delicious inventions.
I hope you all try it with seasonings and stuff you have at home.
If you think it looks good, please click the "Good" button, leave a comment, or subscribe to our channel!
Subscribe to our channel!
See you soon, Iris!